LISHA PAYNE

lisha@nyu.edu / Brooklyn, NY 11216 lishap.github.io/portfolio



SKILLS

Mac OS & Windows. Adobe Creative Suite, Figma, GitHub. Experience with WordPress, HTML/CSS, JavaScript, Java, p5.js and C++. Comfortable with hand, power and machine woodworking tools. Analog and digital photography, processing, scanning and enlarger/ink jet printing & screen printing.

TRAINING
AND
EDUCATION

The Rabbit 2023, Game Development Residency Medienboard Berlin-Brandenburg, Germany

Interactive Media Arts B.F.A.

New York University's Tisch School Of The Arts
3.8, graduated cum laude

WORK EXPERIENCE

Ask me about my 6+ years of retail, bar and dining customer service experience!

FREELANCE

Web Designer/Developer

- May 2022 → current in Brooklyn, NY
- Created a portfolio website for 3 clients using Figma, HTML5, CSS3, and JavaScript.
- Improved the frontend and content management system for the client's website.
- Analyzed a client website for web accessibility using WCAG 2.0 standards and provided a report with findings and suggestions for improvements, then programmed adjustments in collaboration with a team of product owners.

INTERACTIVE TELE COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM AT NYU

Floor Staff

September 2018 → May 2022 in Brooklyn, NY

- Checked in and out audio, visual and electronic equipment to students, residents and faculty, over 50x per day.
- Organized and inventoried equipment in 15+ equipment cages and classrooms.
- Provided support for faculty and students in managing, learning, and using equipment by explaining the proper use, assisting with proper hookup and helping students and faculty to troubleshoot equipment problems.

ΙFΧ

Product Design Intern

October 2018 → August 2021 in New York, NY

- Formatting and reworked copy for personal ads, 50x per day.
- Assisted with design of user interface for iOS and Android for the beta mobile application.
- Front-end web design and copywriting for the company website.
- Managed a bug logging and reporting system for the product manager to log bugs in the app and send them to a developer, 25x per day.

WHEELHOUSE CREATIVE

Production and Editing Assistant

August 2017 → June 2022 in New York, NY

- Logged dailies 20x per day for the feature film, The World Before Your Feet (2018), executively produced by Jesse Eisenberg and directed by Jeremy Workman.
- Assisted on production for both on-location and studio sets
- Edited sequences using Adobe Premiere to create rough cuts